<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
 <title>Tom Preston-Werner</title>
 <link href="http://tom.preston-werner.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://tom.preston-werner.com/"/>
 <updated>2012-08-24T22:27:31+03:00</updated>
 <id>http://tom.preston-werner.com/</id>
 <author>
   <name>Tom Preston-Werner</name>
   <email>tom@mojombo.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>The battle for mobile supremacy: fought by lawyers, not techies.</title>
   <link href="http://tom.preston-werner.com/The-Battle-For-Mobile-Supremacy"/>
   <updated>2012-09-01T00:00:00+03:00</updated>
   <id>http://tom.preston-werner.com/The-Battle-For-Mobile-Supremacy</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-battle-for-mobile-supremacy-fought-by-lawyers-not-techies&quot;&gt;The battle for mobile supremacy: fought by lawyers, not techies.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;!-- excerpt start --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Samsung shipped 10 million Galaxy S3’s in the first month that it offered the phone. Apple sold XX million over the same period. Impressive figures but the next frontier for both these countries will be fought in the court room and no longer in the lab.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- excerpt end --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The background to the story has been rehashed all over the internet, but the crux of the story is that Apple is suing Samsuns for $XXm for “” in Australia, Germany, &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>About iterate</title>
   <link href="http://tom.preston-werner.com/About"/>
   <updated>2012-08-23T00:00:00+03:00</updated>
   <id>http://tom.preston-werner.com/About</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;about-iterate&quot;&gt;About iterate&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;!-- excerpt start --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Try. Fail. Try again. Fail. Try one more time. Succeed. Repeat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I was a kid I wanted to be a rocket scientist. Somewhere in between I ended up finding myself knee-deep in photography, financial modelling, mario kart, and football amongst other things. One day I’ll be able to tell you which of those I was any good at.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- excerpt end --&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;so-why-does-this-exist&quot;&gt;So, why does this exist?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are so many people doing things that would have seemed impossible a few years ago but are commonplace today. This blog is about those things that amaze, confuse, intrigue, or even annoy me in some way. Technology of all kinds, innovative companies, people I admire, music, and Kenya are all likely topics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;where-are-you&quot;&gt;Where are you?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to get in touch, discuss some ideas, or anything else, you can find me on &lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/shaun_g&quot;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://ke.linkedin.com/in/shaungithuku&quot;&gt;linkedin&lt;/a&gt;, or elsewhere on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://flavors.me/shaun_githuku&quot;&gt;internet&lt;/a&gt; if you’re so inclined.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Any sufficiently advanced technology is indistinguishable from magic
&lt;cite&gt;Arthur C. Clarke&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>